https://www.wildernesscollege.com/privacy-policy.html

Menu
HomeCoursesRegisterAbout UsFAQeNewsArticlesBlogSearchContact Us
Alderleaf's Privacy Policy
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types
of personal information we receive and collect when you use our website, wildernesscollege.com, as
well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will
help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.
Alderleaf Wilderness College strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness
and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting
our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
Personal Information
Alderleaf collects personally identifiable information from the visitors
to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a
voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name
and telephone number.
This information is collected if you request information from us, and sign up to join our email list or request
some other service or information from us. If you purchase a product or service from us, we will collect your name, email address, phone, billing address and credit card number. The information collected is
internally reviewed, and used to improve the content of our website, notify
our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, we discard it or store it in our files. If we
make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable
information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal
information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes
and will not be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are
identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your
web browser to enable our system to recognize your browser.
The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have come to the
site for the first time, or have returned to a specific page. If you
personalize the site's pages, or register with any of our site's services, a
cookie enables Alderleaf to recall your specific information on
subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying settings in
your browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able
to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a
single website or collection of sites. Beacons are also referred to as web
bugs. They are commonly used by sites that use third-party services to monitor
traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how
visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a website.
As you browse this website, Google Analytics cookies will be
placed on your computer to collect demographic and interest information, but
we do not tie the cookie to any personal information that you provide to us.
If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you may use
their opt-out tool... https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.
Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses the
DoubleClick cookie to serve ads. This cookie enables Google to serve ads to
users based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the
use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google
ad and content network privacy policy.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies automatically, or notify you
when a cookie is being requested. Privacy software can be used to override web
beacons. Taking either of these actions should not cause a problem with our
site, should you so choose.Affiliate ProductsWe receive an affiliate commission for some of the products, mostly books, sold on wildernesscollege.com. The affiliate platform we use is Amazon. By clicking on certain products, you consent to Amazon's use of cookies, as outlined in this link: Amazon privacy policy.Retargeting Ads and Tracking PixelsWildernesscollege.com uses Facebook pixels to determine the effectiveness of some Facebook ad campaigns. You can change your Facebook ad settings here.Wildernesscollege.com contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. However, once you have used them to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. These sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Always exercise caution by reviewing the privacy statement of the website in question before continuing to use it.Children's Online Privacy Protection ActThis website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the
age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online
Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal
information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally
identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual
users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements
around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a
whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not
shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If wildernesscollege.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through
your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a
part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue.
In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in
control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the
purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.Data StoragePersonally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site is stored on our host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada. Some information is collected by third-party services. These include Aweber.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to
protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information
through our website and would like that information deleted from our records,
or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us
page.
Updates and Effective Date
Alderleaf reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is
a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that
our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy
policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will
know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to Alderleaf's privacy policy as posted here on this
website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
HomeCoursesRegisterAbout UsFAQeNewsArticlesBlogSearchContact Us
Call:
(360) 793-8709Office Hours: Tues & Thurs, 10am-4pm, PST
The Six Keys to Survival:Get a free copy of our survival mini-guide and monthly tips! Learn more
Visit the Course Calendar:
×
The Six Keys to Wilderness SurvivalGet a Free Copy of our Survival Mini-Guide and Monthly Wilderness Skills Tips!
Join the free Alderleaf eNewsletter for instant access.
